Yeah, mind running that by me once more?
Elulu will fulfill her destiny of becoming Exasian by offering up her life.
Wait, Exasian is some kind of weapon! What's that got to do with her?
Everything! This weapon will defeat the Demon Lord.
The blade shall only manifest when a dragonkin girl-born human sacrifices her life in exchange.
Screw the legend! Elulu shouldn't have to die!
Seventy percent of the world is already under the Demon Lord's control.
Seventy?
Hordes of monsters devour the innocent while evil demonkin burn down entire towns.
Giants have been destroying one castle after another.
Some villages remain, but almost every kingdom has been overthrown.
The one surviving stronghold is Rosegard Castle.
Any safe locations you've seen recently will fall soon, if they haven't already.
With all the back and forth to the Divine Realm, we haven't really had a chance to assess the situation properly.
Tis only a matter of time before the whole world is under their control.
If the Demon Lord is not slain, Gaya Brande will be doomed.
Elulu, I must admit, I envy you.
You are the power that will save us from this evil.
The Sacred Sword to strike down the Demon Lord.
One of the highest honors among the dragonkin.
Thank you. It's my pleasure.
The Sacred Sword ceremony shall take place tonight.
Feel free to spend the remaining time you have among your friends.
Are you sure about all this?
All this? You mean...
It would be awesome to save the world. Don't get me wrong.
But do you have to die for that to happen?
If that's my destiny, then what choice do I have?
She said that it was a pretty big honor, too.
Maybe so, but still...
All I've ever wanted was to be helpful.
This may not be how I pictured it, but my wish is coming true.
Elulu.
Hey, Rista. The only reason you came here is to save our world, right?
That means my sacrifice will be for a goddess, too.
Kinda.
I didn't realize how bad things were until now.
I know my mission is to defeat the Demon Lord and save this world.
But at what cost?
Hey, Saya?
Yes, sir. We call these Speed Seeds.
Won't find a product like this in any human market.
For every seed you consume, your speed increases for a solid ten minutes.
You better not be lying.
If so, you'll regret it.
I'll sue your scaly ass.
You're so selfish!
Maybe try considering someone else for once?
You know, take Elulu, for example?
What's to consider?
She's gotta do what she's gotta do.
Why should I even have to say anything about it?
That's true!
You're right!
This is my destiny, not yours!
Hey, Lulu!
There is no need to stand on ceremony.
The villagers who prepared this feast would be saddened if you did not partake.
Fine, but where's Elulu?
The Chosen One is getting ready.
She will be with us soon enough.
That's good to hear.
We made cookies!
Please, try some!
Sure!
Thanks so much!
We did our very best making them, so I hope you'll try one too!
Eat one or suffer!
Huh?
It is time.
and now it is upon us let the sacred sword ceremony commence the dragon abyss within the
magic circle created by the first dragon emperor once the girl leaps her flesh and blood will be
assimilated transforming her into exasian the blessed blade will bring with it an end to the
demon lord no not yet stop this well i suppose this is goodbye huh oh and saya i'd hate to rush so make
sure you polish me once i become your sword okay child make haste throw yourself into the dragon
abyss and fulfill your destiny is this really what's right i don't care if she's saving the
world i can't let her do this move it let go of me hey stop it no please listen my dear you're not
having second thoughts are you shall we encourage her hey let her go what you're doing now is just
murder this is like a cult mentality don't do it
come let us cast the girl down into the abyss
what have you done you're here but why i said i shouldn't have to say anything what do i gotta
spell it out for you you're supposed to carry my equipment you can't do that if you're a stupid
sword i don't care about either one of their destinies they made a commitment to me yeah but
if alelu doesn't become exasian what are we gonna do it's fine we don't even know if this thing is real
much less all-powerful how dare you the first dragon emperor foretold it and you believed him
you do realize i make zero sense sounds like some lame lizard on a power trip what you impudent buffoon
what do you find so amusing surely you're not as absurd as this hero surely you intend to save
this world and thwart the demon lord of course i swear to you we will still find a way to rescue
this world but we refuse to sacrifice the life of our friend in the process there's some way to
defeat the demon lord without exasian and if anyone can do it say you can such a shame you are as
daft as the hero you champion you think nothing of our plight and only of yourselves our world may
already be lost screw you you hack the real selfish one here is you
elulu just hang in there no mash are you okay huh this is weird thankfully i am rather cautious
i had a hunch this might transpire which is why the food you ate earlier was laced with a paralytic
prank those cookies we made you had that paralysis stuff baked into them too no spell or antidote can
counter this why even the goddess has been affected none of us can move now then let us proceed with
the ceremony will someone take the initiative and cast a lulu into the abyss please
get out of there oh stop get your damn heads off her
what he can move impossible how are you even standing at all your special ingredient can't work
if i never ate it liar i saw you eat a cookie yeah but did you see me hurl it back up like five
seconds later the thought of some slimy lizard making my food was grody enough to make me barf
hey that's rude says the twerp who just tried to poison me i was on to you long before now though
besides as a rule i only eat food made by that indecent immortal
i have so many feelings i mean not actual feelings but with the poison and everything
the paralysis can't freeze the heat between us
damn i'll make you a million snacks if you keep looking like one
you leave me no other choice i have no wish to get violent with he who shall bear the sacred sword
but i will do what i must seems i must knock some sense into your unoccupied head
fine come at me bro
so confident however you should not underestimate me behold the magnificence of the chosen dragon kin
dragon god metamorphosis
that hp hurts she's too strong
the scales of a dragon are tougher than any metal known to man
ordinary swords don't cut it in any sense of the phrase
you may have fought monsters but we dragons are in a league of our own
yo taters
you packed that thing in this bag right
yes sir
inconceivable
how does someone like you have a dragon killer sword
i would have to be pretty freaking stupid to willingly walk into a dragon's den without some sort of dragon slaying weapon
ha ha i don't think i've ever been so happy to have such a paranoid hero
that's awesome master but where did you even get that thing
synthesis duh
i used a platinum sword a strand of hair from you and a lulu since you're both dragon kin
and then i helped myself to a hundred of rista's hairs
ah a hundred
how did you get your hands on that many of my precious hairs
by plucking them from you while you were sleeping of course
ah not by me again
you did what while i was sleeping
oh a jerk
he's lucky he's hot while he's ignoring me
get it together rista
he needs to concentrate on fighting
calm down remember after all this is over
you're gonna make him spill his guts
atomic split slash attack
i did not expect so much damage even from a dragon killer
and yet
not bad
hey be careful
you wouldn't want to crush the main ingredient for your super sword
really nothing says the girl must be alive when she enters the abyss
all that is needed is her flesh and blood nothing more
you suck
yes i see
you will protect the girl no matter what the cost
what a shame
i am rather cautious though
no hey lulu
what's your scaly butt up to now
i triggered the death sentence necklace
the instant its black light encircles her neck
a lulu's life will be snuffed out
enjoy your last three minutes amongst the living
a cursed item
curses aren't cautious at all
the child is destined to die
i act to save our entire world
screw you
hey
listen lamezilla
you're not with the demon lord
so i'm giving you one fair warning
lift the curse you put on her or else
oh you fascinate me
issuing such threats
even though i hold all the power
the sword ceremony is fate
to lift the curse and defy fate
you will have to kill me
sounds good
then i guess i can stop holding back
phoenix drive
he's frying her to a crisp
let's see
snapdragon
he's nearly got her down to half her hp
there is no denying how strong you are hero
but it will take more than brute strength to reverse a curse
i have activated my ultimate wall and assumed this glorious form
your attacks will now have the same effect as a light passing breeze
then i'll just have to tear that wall down
oh he looks like a little hamster but sexy
speed seeds baby
a second dragon killer
seriously
this is my spare one
i like to have a backup just in case
but i can also use it for this
go double eternal sword mode
he's combining the eternal sword technique
with a back full of speed seeds
and dual dragon killers
if you believe yourself bloody hero
then come on
sure thing
go seiyah
you're doing great
i don't get him
he's barely even phasing her
my ultimate wall is the supreme hardening technique
take pride in the insignificant damage you have managed to cause
speaking of futile
the child has nearly succumbed to the curse
there is no saving her
why not cease this senseless struggle and accept the inevitable
seiyah
that's enough okay
eilulu
i appreciate it
i can see how hard you're fighting to save my life
but you can stop it now
oh no
maybe she is destined to be a sword
it just doesn't make sense that we'd have to go so far to save this world
it is time you admit defeat hero
just as it is time eilulu dies
justice will prevail
you're right
and just what do you mean by that hero
then you call yourself cautious
give me a break
stop this at once
cease your advance
live the curse and it'll stop
it's not rocket science
how perplexing
why go so far to protect such a useless wealth
the only worthwhile contribution she could ever hope to make would be in the form of the sacred sword
otherwise she is nothing but scum
she's not scum
she hauls bags
scum can't do that
it's true
well that may not have been sweet or even very nice
but at least it was genuine
i guess i'll speak my piece too
release her
or kiss your dragon back goodbye
oh right i forfeit the curse has been lifted so hard to attack
fool the only thing i lifted was my ultimate wall
you shall die too
dragon breath
double winged blade
true i may have lost my footing
but i still have my wings
no my wings but but how
yeah that went well
the nose dive must have ended both levi and her curse
yay lulu
you're okay
sorry
no don't worry about it
i think i'm still paralyzed
it's fine
how long before the stupid
just curious
when exactly did you damage levi's wings
it was before she activated her ultimate wall ability
i had a feeling she'd switch to defense pretty early on
my normal strategy would have been to take her out hard and fast
but her hp was almost god tier
so i had no choice but to improvise
i focused on backing her into a corner and cutting off any means of escape
this forced me to deal with her wall but it also supplied me with a distraction she couldn't help but fall for
and here i was thinking you couldn't get any more cautious
well i had a source monster
help shape my strategy
that dragon lady sure was a lot like a nurikabe
you're clueless about slimes but a bro at all about nurikabe
yeah that yosube
i can't believe that crusty lizard lady thought she was cautious
if it were me i would have had my ultimate wall up back during the feast
right because that wouldn't have been suspicious at all
levi how could this be
what are we going to do
what is that
oh look
the magic circle in the abyss must have turned levi into a sword
she did say that ixation required the flesh blood and life of a female who bore the blood of the dragons
as bogus as it sounds she's become a sword
which would mean
get rista to heal you
belulu's flesh and blood are part of the sword now
how positively divine
wait out about it
just look
that's it
ixation
hmm the blade that will defeat the demon lord
pretty sweet accomplishment you dragonkin just nabbed for yourselves
there's nothing like a win-win
but levi just tragically met a demise
she would have wanted to offer her life if it meant saving the world
she even said so herself when she was alive
well i suppose that's true
so it's a win-win
no one is sad
really
because i feel sad
you guys got what you wanted right
so if you have ignatian and you know it
clap your hands
and we're right back where we started
thank you so much
i've never been that scared in my whole life
knock it off short stack
you good
you know something
please don't laugh
but when they told me i was going to die
i was most sad about not being able to talk to you ever again
whoa i felt the same
is it just me or is there some serious chemistry in the air
love and adventure do tend to go hand in hand
hey guys i have an idea
why don't you two go on ahead of us
okay but why would we do that
you just said you like talking to each other
besides say and i need to have a little chat also
oh okay
right
we'll wait over by the entrance
oh isn't that the cutest
not my thing
whatever
we really do need to have a little chat though
it's about your dragon killers
so uh you plucked out 100 of my hairs
so what if i did
i swear if you make me go bald because of your stupid sticky fingers
you will regret it
you didn't do anything else while i was asleep right
what do you mean by that
well you know there are all sorts of things that can happen while a lady is unconscious and vulnerable
i'm not like that and you're not a lady
that doesn't make it okay
you can't just steal someone's hair you freak
you're lucky i'm not pressing charges
what do you think would have happened to a lulu without those two swords
quit being so dramatic
hold up we are not done here
i think we are
that sword
it's not really exaceon huh
what
did you forget i'm a goddess
i can sense that weapon is severely lacking in sacred power
you just might be smarter than you look blondie
because you're right
this thing is an exaceon
it's a platinum sword plus i made myself
you lied to an entire village about that sword
wanted to put their minds at ease
you know this is gonna have to stay our little secret right
i know
i'm just wondering if levier was right
what if exaceon is the only weapon that can defeat the demon lord
then we'll just have to kick his ass some other way
i mean you said so yourself didn't you
i was kind of caught up in the moment
it's gonna be okay
have faith
let's go
the dragon brats are waiting
all right that was definitely the most unsealike thing i've ever heard
maybe he's tired and not thinking straight
once we get back to the village we'll catch up on some sleep
hey we got company
like a lot
all is in readiness precisely as you commanded
the hero will be of no significance to you now
good
we will now have the ability to destroy even the gods of heaven
during the days time
ev fret
КОРЬ I ROW
ДИНАМИ
ЕЛЬМУ
ЕЛЬМ
ЕЛ DO
ЕЛЬМУ
勇気よさも君は特別すぎたよ
魔法だって解けない謎の横顔で
見つめた明日はぐれ星を巡るの
何度目サプライジング
嫌だねどこ行くの
ここではぐれたらノーマルーン
離さないであなたへお願いは一個だけ
Be perfect please be perfect please
未来はきっと繋いだ糸
遠く細いけど輝いは絆
確かめた追いつけないオラバラスライン
刻んでそっと痛いな一歩
愛想のない大きな手のひら
心配なプリズムなの
光
愛のために
世界の鍵
本当の勇気は
In your hand
抱きしめるよ